{
  "count": 42,
  "pairs": [
    {
      "question": "I really hope you all change but I'm sure you won't! Because you don't have to!",
      "answer": "Your business means a lot to us. Please DM your name, zip code and additional details about your concern. ^RR"
    },
    {
      "question": "see attached error message. I've tried leaving a voicemail several times in the past week",
      "answer": "Have you tried from another device, Miriam ^MM"
    },
    {
      "question": "yep, I've tried laptop too several times over the past week and again today. I've tried different browsers too",
      "answer": "It's working OK from here, Miriam. Does this link help ? ^MM"
    },
    {
      "question": "I still haven't heard &amp; the number I'm directed to by phone is a dead end &amp; the live chat doesn't work. Can someone call me?",
      "answer": "LiveChat is online at the moment - or contact 03331 031 031 option 1, 4, 3 (Leave a message) to request a call back"
    },
    {
      "question": "Me too am suffering , hope the can find a solution",
      "answer": "We can help. Which version of iOS are you on? You can find that in Settings &gt; General &gt; About. Reply in DM."
    },
    {
      "question": "I just updated my phone and suddenly everything takes ages to load wtf this update sux I hate it fix it bye",
      "answer": "Thanks for reaching out to us. We are always happy to help. Send us a DM so we can look into this together."
    },
    {
      "question": "Thanks! Version 8.4.22.857 armv7 on anker bluetooth speaker on Samsung Galaxy Tab A (2016) Model SM-T280 Does distance from speaker matter?",
      "answer": "Thanks. The distance could possibly affect playback. Does logging out &gt; restarting your device &gt; logging back in make a difference? /AY"
    },
    {
      "question": "No, but I've moved speaker to about 1 metre away and it's not skipping at the mo - it was about 3 or 4 metres away before. Fingers crossed!",
      "answer": "That's great to hear. If anything comes up, just let us know. We'll carry on helping out ðŸ™‚ /AY"
    },
    {
      "question": "Brilliant thanks ðŸ˜Š",
      "answer": "You're welcome! If there's anything else we can help with, just give us a shout. We're here for you ðŸ˜‰ /CP"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please help! Spotify Premium skipping through songs constantly on android tablet &amp; bluetooth speaker. Tried everything!",
      "answer": "Hi there! What device is this happening on? If you could also let us know the Android and Spotify versions you're using, that'd be great /AY"
    },
    {
      "question": "after the 11.0.2 my phone just sucks most of the apps are broken, wifi disconnects frequently #apple #ios1102 #painfulupdate",
      "answer": "We'd love to help! Please DM us and let us know any steps you've tried since experiencing these behaviors."
    },
    {
      "question": "First flight for long time with . Now over one 1h delay for the short jump FRA-LCY and NO one here to provide status updates",
      "answer": "We're sorry your flight has been delayed, Beatner. Are you travelling on the BA8733? If so, the updated departure time we have is 15:30. 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Okay I used my fucking phone for 2 minutes and it drains it down 8 fucking percent",
      "answer": "Battery life is important, and we're here for you. DM us the iOS version your iPhone is running. We'll go from there."
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you get my iPhone 7plus back on the old iOS please? Battery runs out in half the time, apps now frequently crash.",
      "answer": "Thanks for reaching out to us. We are always happy to help. Send us a DM so we can look into this together."
    },
    {
      "question": "Youâ€™ve paralysed my phone with your update grrrrrrrrrr",
      "answer": "We'd be happy to help. Send us a DM and we can start there."
    },
    {
      "question": "I received this a few weeks ago, since then I've been getting 2/3 calls a day from a telemarketer. Is someone using your name?",
      "answer": "ðŸ¤” We'd like to help Sam, which number is calling you? Please DM us more info so we can advise further."
    },
    {
      "question": "My internet is down and xfinity talkin about 24-72 hours... yâ€™all have the game messed up.",
      "answer": "I understand this is a frustrating experience, please send a DM with your account information so I can look into this matter for you. -AD"
    },
    {
      "question": "I service last 40 min sprint can I get a refund",
      "answer": "I understand how you frustrated this situation can be. Please follow us by sending a DM for further assistance. Sprint Cares. -AC"
    },
    {
      "question": "So the new update does not let me listen to music and go on whatsapp at the same time?!?",
      "answer": "We'd like to help. What happens when you try to listen to Apple Music &amp; use WhatsApp? Does the music pause? Let us know in DM."
    },
    {
      "question": "seems to be working at this stage. Will let you know if it happens again. Cheers",
      "answer": "Sure thing. We'll keep an eye out for your update /MU"
    },
    {
      "question": "problem has come back again today. is there some kind of bug?",
      "answer": "Thanks for giving us a nudge about this. What device, operating system, and Spotify version is this happening on? /AY"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's on a Macbook Air (early 2014), running High Sierra, spotify version 1.0.65.320.gac7a8e02",
      "answer": "Got it. Can you try the steps here for us: They should help with this. Let us know how it plays out /AY"
    },
    {
      "question": "i've been having issues with playback. songs have been stopping midway through and won't restart unless i close and reopen app",
      "answer": "Hi Harry! Help's here. Can you check if logging out &gt; restarting your device &gt; logging back in makes a difference? Keep us posted /MU"
    },
    {
      "question": "#ios11update - is still killing my battery within 12 hours - phone is 10 months old - itâ€™s a disgrace - used to get 2 days",
      "answer": "Let's take a look. What is the exact iOS you're using? Are you using any specific apps when noticing this? DM us your reply."
    },
    {
      "question": "Took my phone off charge at 7:20am. 8:03am - 60% battery remaining. plz I beg you, sort your battery life outðŸ˜©",
      "answer": "Thanks for reaching out to us. We are always happy to help. Send us a DM so we can look into this together."
    },
    {
      "question": "Just curious....will I get the companion pass the exact moment I get enough points? It will I have to wait? Thanks!",
      "answer": "Once the points load and you hit the number, you get it immediately! You'll even receive a congrats email. Are you almost there? ^AC"
    },
    {
      "question": "I need a new code for my I-store. I havenâ€™t recd any but msg is too many sent. Help!",
      "answer": "We'd like to provide some assistance with this. Tell us more about the issue you're experiencing in DM. We'll go from there."
    },
    {
      "question": "fix this update. Itâ€™s horrible",
      "answer": "Are you experiencing an issue with your device? If so, DM us with what's going on. We'll see how we can help from there."
    },
    {
      "question": "Thanks for your answer. Response onsite was that Aircraft will not depart today, so rebooking to with now 4h delay...",
      "answer": "Very sorry to hear this. We hope you get everything sorted. Kind Regards ^Jools"
    },
    {
      "question": "I guess this means free cable for the neighborhood.",
      "answer": "I am sorry for the poor experience. Can you please DM the full service address and name on the account, as we ass..."
    },
    {
      "question": "The point is if it's enforced they do it properly or they don't. Plus take some common-sense and think does that person look over 18?",
      "answer": "Hi Thomas, if a colleague believes the person buying alcohol looks under 25, they will be challenged for ID to prove they're of age. - Paige"
    },
    {
      "question": "Uk offlicense law is 18. Not 25",
      "answer": "Hi Thomas, this is correct but this helps our store colleagues judge age and protect them from making underage sales. Amanda"
    },
    {
      "question": "Got id's for buying one Adnams Broadside. Is being blind part of the job-spec? I am 35 and 99 kilos.",
      "answer": "Hi Thomas, we operate a Think 25 policy at our stores. I'd be flattered to be ID'd. :-) - Helena"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will I lose all the shopping I've done if I delete the cache/cookies (not using app)?",
      "answer": "Hi there, as long as you sign out of your account prior to deleting your cache &amp; cookies, you'll still have a full basket :) Thanks - Mike"
    },
    {
      "question": "Done all that. Still telling me there are no delivery slots whatsoever.",
      "answer": "Can you DM me your full name, address and email? I'd be happy to look into this further for you :) Thanks - Mike"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hey , your website's broken. It's telling me there are no delivery slots for the next 3 weeks, which I find slightly unlikely.",
      "answer": "Hi there, could you try deleting your cache and cookies and reinstalling the app if using it? This should fix the issue :) - Dani"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have the latest version iOS. It started immediately after I updated my phone.",
      "answer": "Is there a particular app that seems to cause these issues more than others? What model iPhone are you using? Join us in DM."
    },
    {
      "question": "My apps stop working without warning and my phone freezes every five minutes! Love the new update !!!!",
      "answer": "We'd like to help if we can. When did this start happening? Which version of iOS are you running currently?"
    },
    {
      "question": "Problem with printhead Serial# TH536D1HN #hpcswus #hpprnt",
      "answer": "Hi Agoura, thanks for tweeting. Please refer to this article: &amp; click the link to reply back. ^Rashmi"
    },
    {
      "question": "I wish Amazon had an option of where I can just get it shipped to the ups store so I can avoid a lot of the struggle",
      "answer": "UPS has a service called My Choice that will allow your packages to be delivered to UPS Store. ^ML"
    },
    {
      "question": "They reschedule my shit for tomorrow",
      "answer": "I wish Amazon had an option of where I can just get it shipped to the ups store so I can avoid a lot of the struggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "bit of both - finding the layout cumbersome and when removing an item from faves - getting a huge slowdown. Not keen on the thin green line",
      "answer": "If that doesn't help please DM your full name, address and email including the browser and device so we can log this. Thanks - Lee 2/2"
    }
  ]
}